Andrew Tran

Full Stack Web Developer

trandrew96@gmail.com

Vancouver Island, BC

<u>LinkedIn</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 2 years of full stack web development experience. I am dedicated to writing high-quality code, and my attention to detail extends to designing UI that exceeds user expectations. I am committed to continuous learning and am eager to make meaningful contributions. You can explore some of my personal projects which showcase my skills and creativity on my personal website transfer.

SKILLS

Programming languages

- Javascript
- Python
- CSS/HTML

Frameworks

- React
- Tailwind CSS
- Node

Databases

- SQL
- MongoDB

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Consultant

Town of Lake Cowichan | Lake Cowichan BC | 05/2023 - 09/2023

- Consult with client to develop and document Website requirements
- Plan, design, write, modify, integrate and test Web-site related code (html, php)
- Bug fixes

Full-Stack Web Developer Co-op

Ergonomyx | Victoria BC | 09/2020 - 05/2021

- Design, develop, and update UI
- Build full-stack features (django, express, node.js)
- Update and maintain APIs

Junior Web Developer Co-op

ACD Systems | Victoria BC | 01/2019 - 08/2019

Implement static web pages using PHP (symfony), html, CSS

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Software Engineering, 2021

The University of Victoria, Victoria BC

REFERENCES

Ronnie Gill Supervisor at Lake Cowichan rgill@lakecowichan.ca

Sergio Perez Project Manager at Ergonomyx sergio@ergonomyx.com